Guide to the Arthur Einstein Papers, 1978-2001 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1990-2001 and undated
  - RL10039-VHS-0240. Seitzer & Miller Advertising. 1997. VHS. AXA/Equitable spots, 1:00. (Box AV8)
  - RL10039-VHS-0241. Seitzer & Miller Advertising. 1997. VHS. AXA/Equitable spots, 1:00. (Box AV8)
  - RL10039-VHS-0242. Select Communications, Agency Reel. 1997 Sept. 9. VHS. Eau de Veino spots, 3:35. (Box AV8)
  - RL10039-VHS-0243. Sights and Sounds. Undated. VHS. WTDT (Worldwide Target Demographic Television) #101. (Box AV8)
  - RL10039-VHS-0244. Slater Hanft Martin, Agency Reel. 1993 Jan. 19. VHS. Bic, Sony, Thompson's Waterseal, Shop Vac, Chaos record label. (Box AV8)
  - RL10039-VHS-0245. Slater Hanft Martin, Agency Reel. Undated. VHS. Bic, Sony, Thompson's Waterseal, Crohn's and Colitis Foundation. (Box AV8)
  - RL10039-VHS-0246. Slaughter Hanson, Demo Reel. Undated. VHS. (Box AV8)
  - RL10039-VHS-0247. Stein Robaire Helm. Undated. VHS. 8 spots. (Box AV8)
  - RL10039-VHS-0248. Sunkist K.I.D.S. 55. Undated. VHS. WTDT (Worldwide Target Demographic Television). (Box AV8)
  - RL10039-VHS-0249. Tieche and Company. Undated. VHS. (Box AV8)
  - RL10039-VHS-0250. Tracy Locke. Compaq Questionnaire Broadcast Reel. 1991 Sept. 26. VHS. (Box AV8)
  - RL10039-VHS-0251. Trone, Broadcast reel. 1997 June 18. VHS. (Box AV8)
  - RL10039-VHS-0252. Trumpet Advertising. Undated. VHS. (Box AV8)
  - RL10039-VHS-0253. Public Sector Solutions, Sample Reel #4. 1994 Apr. 27. VHS. 31 spots, includes NBO Stores, Shoe-Town, Partners National Health Plans, American Red Cross, Boston Summer Jobs, Harvard Community Health, Planned Parenthood, MTA, Chemical Bank, New England Telephone. (Box AV8)
  - RL10039-VHS-0254. Vogt/Wein. Undated. VHS. (Box AV8)
  - RL10039-VHS-0255. Vogt/Wein. 1996. VHS. Samsung spots, 1:30. (Box AV8)
  - RL10039-VHS-0256. Vogt/Wein. Undated. VHS. Samsung spots. (Box AV9)
  - RL10039-VHS-0257. Waring & LaRosa, agency reel. Undated. VHS. (Box AV9)
  - RL10039-VHS-0258. Warwick Baker O'Neill. 1998. VHS. Fruit of the Loom spots, 1:30. (Box AV9)
  - RL10039-VHS-0259. Warwick Baker O'Neill. Undated. VHS. National Guard, Tia. (Box AV9)
  - RL10039-VHS-0260. Warwick Baker O'Neill. Undated. VHS. Knorr, Panasonic, National Guard, Fruit of the Loom case history. (Box AV9)
  - RL10039-VHS-0261. Waylon Ad. Undated. VHS. Aetna, Busch beer, U.S. Healthcare, St. Louis Cardinals, St. Louis Blues Heritage Festival, United Van Lines. (Box AV9)
  - RL10039-VHS-0262. W.B. Doner & Co. Undated. VHS. Coca-Cola Christmas Caravan, 2:00. (Box AV9)
  - RL10039-VHS-0263. Welch Nehlen Groome Advertising (NHG), Agency Reel. Undated. VHS. Adecco, North Shore-Lij, Getsmart, Newsday. (Box AV9)
  - RL10039-VHS-0264. Well, Here's What the Experts Think. Undated. VHS. Eagle Vision, 6:30. (Box AV9)
  - RL10039-VHS-0265. Wells Rich Greene BDDP. Undated. VHS. (Box AV9)
  - RL10039-VHS-0266. Wells Rich Greene BDDP, Creative Reel for Oppenheimer Funds. 1996 Apr. 19. VHS. Tag Heuer, Chase, Hertz, Ford, Heineken, Dun & Bradstreet, Clairol, Ad Council. (Box AV9)
  - RL10039-VHS-0267. Wells Rich Greene BDDP. Undated. VHS. Chase Manhattan spots, 2:30. (Box AV9)
  - RL10039-VHS-0268. Wells Rich Greene BDDP. Undated. VHS. Ford, Seagram's, Mobil, Liberty Mutual, Hertz, Midas, Oil of Olay, New York State, IBM. (Box AV9)
  - RL10039-VHS-0269. West & Vaughan (renamed French West Vaughan). Undated. VHS. Case studies: Central Carolina Bank (CCB), Fix a Flat, Biscuitville. (Box AV9)
  - RL10039-VHS-0270. Wieden & Kennedy TV. Undated. VHS. (Box AV9)
  - RL10039-VHS-0271. William Cook Agency. Undated. VHS. 10 How-To's of Advertising. (Box AV9)
  - RL10039-VHS-0272. Woolward & Partners, Television Spots Demo Master. 1993 June 30. VHS. Running time 6:00. (Box AV9)
  - RL10039-VHS-0273. WPA Sample Reel. 1992. VHS. (Box AV9)
  - RL10039-VHS-0274. Zero Base Advertising. Undated. VHS. Ohio Health Services, OhioHealth Network, 4:30. (Box AV9)
  - RL10039-VHS-0275. Ziccardi & Partners. Undated. VHS. (Box AV9)
  - RL10039-VHS-0276. Ammirati & Puris, Creative Reel. Undated. VHS. BMW, UPS, RCA, Aetna, Cadbury-Schweppes, Arrow Shirt, Stanley Works, Sterling Health. (Box AV9)
  - RL10039-VHS-0277. Anderson & Lembke TV. Undated. VHS. A&L logo; Fore Systems, Corporate, SAP America, IQNY, ILUVNY, Dow Jones, Sharp, Handgun Control, logo, 5:10. (Box AV9)
  - RL10039-VHS-0278. Angotti, Thomas Hedge. Undated. VHS. Saab, Foster's, Barron's, RCN, Fuhi, MONY, Per Diem, Maalox. (Box AV9)
  - RL10039-VHS-0279. Arnold Communications, general agency reel. Undated. VHS. VW, Titleist, Foot-Joy, Pinnacle, Blue Cross/Blue Shield, NYNEX, Fleet, McDonald's, Kinney, Allied. (Box AV9)
  - RL10039-VHS-0280. Bates USA Creative Examples. 1998 Feb. 23. VHS. (Box AV9)
  - RL10039-VHS-0281. Butler, Shine & Stern. 1994 June.VHS. San Francisco Jazz Festival, Barilla/Germany, Northgate Mall, 3DO, Crystal Dynamics, Artichoke Joe's Casino, Isuzu, Soho Soda, Grandy's Restaurants. (Box AV9)
  - RL10039-VHS-0282. Butler, Shine & Stern. Undated. VHS. Allbusiness.com, Homewarehouse.com, 989 Studios, Borders Book & Music, Miller's Outpost, San Francisco Food Bank, Metamarkets.com, 6:30. (Box AV9)
  - RL10039-VHS-0283. Campbell Mithun Esty Broadcast. 1995 July 6. VHS. Healthy Choice, U.S. West, Andersen, Century 21, Borden, DowBrands, Fridigaire, Toro. (Box AV9)
  - RL10039-VHS-0284. Citigate Albert Frank, presentation. 1998 Feb. 20. VHS. CNF Transportation, Thompson Financial, Jardine Fleming, Dow Jones Asia, AIG, GT Global Millennium Minute. (Box AV9)
  - RL10039-VHS-0285. Citron, Haligman & Bedecarre Agency Reel. Undated. VHS. Dreyfus, Good Guys, Women.com, Homes.com, Sony, Thirdage. (Box AV9)
  - RL10039-VHS-0286. D'Arcy Masius Benton & Bowles (DMB&B), reel for Bankers Trust. Undated. VHS. Eli Lilly, Citizen, Blockbuster, TWA, Dow, Aleve, Cadillac, Lockheed, 1:59. (Box AV9)
  - RL10039-VHS-0287. DDB Needham Dallas, presentation for NationsBank Montgomery. 1998 Feb. 20. VHS. (Box AV9)
  - RL10039-VHS-0288. DDB Needham Worldwide, Presentation to NYSE. 1995 Nov. 16. VHS. New York State Lottery, Digital, Bermuda, Michelin, Cigna, Hershey, Bud Light, Mobil, Lynx, Rold Gold. (Box AV10)
  - RL10039-VHS-0289. Doremus, Presentation to NationsBank Montgomery. 1998 Feb. 24. VHS. (Box AV10)
  - RL10039-VHS-0290. Fallon McElligott agency reel. 1998 Feb. 26. VHS. Timex, Lee Jeans, Miller Lite, BMW, United Airlines, Prudential, Coca-Cola, 9:00. (Box AV10)
  - RL10039-VHS-0291. Fallon McElligott presentation for Compaq. 1991 Nov. 20. VHS. Hush Puppies, Ralston Purina, Porsche, Star Tribune, Penn, Lee Jeans, Crystal Sugar, Amoco, Violence Against Women, Timex. (Box AV10)
  - RL10039-VHS-0292. Fallon McElligott. 1998 Feb. 26. VHS. Continental Bank spots, :45. (Box AV10)
  - RL10039-VHS-0293. Gardner, Geary, Coll & Young (GGC&Y) agency reel. 1998 Apr. VHS. Delta Dental, Lombard, Power Wheels, Fetzer Vineyards, State Fund, Stri-Dex, San Francisco Chronicle, Enabl, California Gold. (Box AV10)
  - RL10039-VHS-0294. Gardner, Geary, Coll & Young (GGC&Y). 1998 Apr. VHS. Montgomery Securities: The Power of Growth. (Box AV10)
  - RL10039-VHS-0295. Gillespie, Port Authority TV Reel. Undated. VHS. (Box AV10)
  - RL10039-VHS-0296. Grace & Rothschild Advertising. 1998 Apr. VHS. Range Rover, Mobil, Discovery, Ermet & Young, J&J Snacks, Mount Sinai, Omnipoint, Bassett Beck. (Box AV10)
  - RL10039-VHS-0297. Grant Jacoby. Undated. VHS. Ideas that Open Doors. (Box AV10)
  - RL10039-VHS-0298. Harris Drury Cohen Agency Demo Reel. 1998 Aug. VHS. (Box AV10)
  - RL10039-VHS-0299. Harris Drury Cohen Agency Reel. Undated. VHS. (Box AV10)
  - RL10039-VHS-0300. Hill/Holliday. Undated. VHS. Cisco Systems, Micronpc.com, Sempra Energy, Sybase, Coca-Cola, Kia, Ameristar Casinos, Aerial Communications, WebMiles.com, Move.com, LucasArts Entertainment, Dreyer's Ice Cream. (Box AV10)
  - RL10039-VHS-0301. Hill/Holliday, Presentation to NationsBank Montgomery. 1998 Apr. VHS. (Box AV10)
  - RL10039-VHS-0302. Howard, Merrell & Partners. 1997. VHS. BB&T brand campaign spots, 3:00. (Box AV10)
  - RL10039-VHS-0303. Lowe, Lintas & Partners. 2000 Aug. VHS. ESPN, Autoweb.com, ZDNet, Charles Schwab, 800.COM, Sun Microsystems, 5:15. (Box AV10)
  - RL10039-VHS-0304. MARC, Agency Sample Reel. Undated. VHS. ServiStar, Rite Aid, Schwebel's, Bryant, Pittsburgh Zoo, Health America, Kennywood. (Box AV10)
  - RL10039-VHS-0305. Margeotes Fertitta & Partners, Presentation to Bankers Trust Company. Undated. VHS. Colonial Williamsburg, New York Newsday, Swiss Army, Jet Dry, NFL, Barilla, USF&G, McGraw-Hill. (Box AV10)
  - RL10039-VHS-0306. Margeotes Fertitta & Partners, Creative Sample Reel for NationsBank Montgomery. 1998 Feb. VHS. MediaOne, Godiva Chocolatier, Partnership for a Drug Free America, NFL Enterprises, McGraw-Hill. (Box AV10)
  - RL10039-VHS-0307. Martin/Williams Advertising. Undated. VHS. Northern States Power Image TV. (Box AV10)
  - RL10039-VHS-0308. McCann-Erickson/A&L, Creative Reel. 2000 Aug. 15. VHS. MSN, Goodwill, Supercuts, Del Monte, Microsoft, Blue Shield. (Box AV10)
  - RL10039-VHS-0309. McKinney & Silver, Agency Reel. 1996 Nov. VHS. (Box AV10)
  - RL10039-VHS-0310. Montgomery Securities. Undated. VHS. The Power of Growth, Corporate Video. (Box AV10)
  - RL10039-VHS-0311. Neiman Group, Radio and TV. Undated. VHS. (Box AV10)
  - RL10039-VHS-0312. New York Stock Exchange (NYSE). Undated. VHS. NYSE Partnership in Communications. (Box AV10)
  - RL10039-VHS-0313. New York Stock Exchange (NYSE). Undated. VHS. NASDAQ commercials. (Box AV10)
  - RL10039-VHS-0314. New York Stock Exchange (NYSE). Undated. VHS. Partners in Communication (nnew version). (Box AV10)
  - RL10039-VHS-0315. New York Stock Exchange (NYSE). Undated. VHS. Ad Agency Review: Leo Burnett 0:00-13:00, Bozell 13:00-19:00, Ammiratti 19:00-28:00, Fallon 28:00-35:00, Goodby 35:00-43:00, DDB Needham 43:00-50:00. (Box AV10)
  - RL10039-VHS-0316. New York Stock Exchange (NYSE). Undated. VHS. The World Puts Its Stock in Us, 9:23. (Box AV10)
  - RL10039-VHS-0317. Partners & Shevack, Reel for Oppenheimer. Undated. VHS. (Box AV10)
  - RL10039-VHS-0318. Rosenfeld, Sirowitz, Humphrey & Strauss, reel for IBM PC. 1993 July 6. VHS. RCCL, Dial, Luzianne Tea, America West Airlines, Redbook, Food Stamps. (Box AV10)
  - RL10039-VHS-0319. TBWA Chiat/Day, Presentation for NationsBank Montgomery. Undated. VHS. Home Savings, New York Life, Drexel Burnham. (Box AV10)
  - RL10039-VHS-0320. TBWA Chiat/Day, Presentation for NationsBank Montgomery. Undated. VHS. Shearson Lehman spots. (Box AV10)
  - RL10039-VHS-0321. TBWA Chiat/Day, Showreel for NationsBank Montgomery. 1998 Jan. VHS. Apple, Weather Channel, Nissan, Jack in the Box, Energizer, Taco Bell, Home Savings, Champion, Infiniti, Nike, Pizza Hut, NYNEX, California Cooler, Arrow, Reebok. (Box AV11)
  - RL10039-VHS-0322. Temerlin McClain, NationsBank Creative Spots. 1998 Feb. 20. VHS. (Box AV11)
  - RL10039-VHS-0323. Temerlin McClain, Creative Reel. 1998 Feb. 20. VHS. (Box AV11)
  - RL10039-VHS-0324. W.B. Doner & Co., Presentation to IBM. Undated. VHS. BP, Chiquita, Red Roof Inns, Motrin, 7-Eleven, B.F. Goodrich, Franco-American, Eckerd Drug, Arby's, Lowe's, National Zoo, Canadian Tire, Greater Michigan Ford. (Box AV11)
  - RL10039-VHS-0325. W.B. Doner & Co. Undated. VHS. Doner Television from the '50s to the '90s. (Box AV11)
  - RL10039-VHS-0326. Wieden & Kennedy, Compilation Reel for NationsBank Montgomery. 1998 Feb. 19. VHS. Microsoft, Nike, Miller, ESPN, Sure Trade, Coca-Cola. (Box AV11)
  - RL10039-3/4-0001. Air Creative Group, Agency Reel. 1997 Sept. 3/4-inch. Disney, CBS, NATPE, KCBS, Paramount. (Box AV11)
  - RL10039-3/4-0002. Ammirati & Puris, Creative Reel. Undated. 3/4-inch. Burger King, UPS, MasterCard, Aetna, Compaq, LaBatt, Stanley, RCA. (Box AV11)
  - RL10039-3/4-0003. Bates USA Creative Examples. 1998 Feb. 23. 3/4-inch. Hyundai, EDS, T. Rowe Price, Provident Bank, Wendy's, Estee Lauder, GTE, Lady Foot Locker, Cinnaburst, Avis, CVS, Indianapolis Ice. (Box AV11)
  - RL10039-3/4-0004. Doremus. Undated. 3/4-inch. Morgan Stanley Webs, 1:30. (Box AV11)
  - RL10039-3/4-0005. Fallon McElligott/Fallon McElligott Berlin, Prudential competitive ad spots. 1996. 3/4-inch. Fidelity, T. Rowe Price, Charles Schwab. (Box AV11)
  - RL10039-3/4-0006. Griffin Bacal. Undated. 3/4-inch. The Griffin Bacal You Don't Know (6:45 But Worth It). (Box AV11)
  - RL10039-3/4-0007. New York Stock Exchange (NYSE). Undated. 3/4-inch. This Week with David Brinkley, John Phelan Insider Trading. (Box AV11)
  - RL10039-3/4-0008. Saatchi & Saatchi Advertising. Undated. 3/4-inch. Bell Atlantic spots, 3:30. (Box AV11)
  - RL10039-3/4-0009. Tieche and Company. Undated. 3/4-inch. (Box AV11)
  - RL10039-3/4-0010. Weiss, Whitten, Carroll, Stagliano, Agency Reel. Undated. 3/4-inch. (Box AV11)
  - RL10039-CS-0001. Arian Lowe & Travis Radio Reel. 1997. Audiocassette. 5 spots, 4:30. (Box AV12)
  - RL10039-CS-0002. Austin Kelley Advertising. Undated. Audiocassette. 6 radio spots, 6:00. (Box AV12)
  - RL10039-CS-0003. Bawden & Associates. Undated. Audiocassette. Marycrest International University commercials, 3:00. (Box AV12)
  - RL10039-CS-0004. Deutsch. Undated. Audiocassette. Mistic spots, 2:00. (Box AV12)
  - RL10039-CS-0005. Gigante Vaz & Partners. Undated. Audiocassette. The Record, City Federal, Top's Appliance City, Ricoh, Shelcore Toys. (Box AV12)
  - RL10039-CS-0006. Gallaspy & Lobel. Undated. Audiocassette. Gilbert Gottfried Radio Show; Client: Dania Jai Alai. 3 spots, 3:00. (Box AV12)
  - RL10039-CS-0007. Goodby, Berlin & Silverstein Radio Demo Reel. Undated. Audiocassette. San Francisco Examiner, Chevy's, Australian Range Lamb, Porsche. (Box AV12)
  - RL10039-CS-0008. Harris Drury Cohen, Agency Radio Demo. Undated. Audiocassette. (Box AV12)
  - RL10039-CS-0009. Harris Drury Cohen, Agency Radio Demo. Undated. Audiocassette. (Box AV12)
  - RL10039-CS-0010. Katz Dochtemann & Epstein (KD&E) Radio. 1995. Audiocassette. Pecorino Romano Cheese, Her New York, Burger King (Michael Bolton), Fund Trust, Toothpaste Booster, Westchester Chevy Geo, American Greetings, Mamma Leone's. (Box AV12)
  - RL10039-CS-0011. Katz Dochtemann & Epstein (KD&E) Radio. 1993. Audiocassette. Goodyear, Her New York, Burger King (Michael Bolton), Final Call, Westchester Chevy Geo, Mamma Leone's. (Box AV12)
  - RL10039-CS-0012. Marsteller Advertising. 1990 Feb. 20. Audiocassette. Perrier radio spots. (Box AV12)
  - RL10039-CS-0013. Pedone & Partners agency radio. Audiocassette. (Box AV12)
  - RL10039-CS-0014. SBC Advertising. Undated. Audiocassette. Provon radio, 1:00. (Box AV12)
  - RL10039-CD-0001. Clarion Marketing and Communications, agency disc.Undated. CD. (Box AV12)
  - RL10039-16MM-0001. Lampert Agency Reel. Undated. 16mm reel. (Box AV11)